6lyrics.com 2011-02-18

# Privacy Policy | 6 Lyrics

Privacy has become a major concern on the Internet. 6lyrics.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This privacy statement describes how 6lyrics.com deals with your information. Some information is collected on this site automatically through our technology; other information is collected only when you choose to give it to us. 

**Personal Information**   
6lyrics.com does not require you to disclose personal information anywhere on the site. However, 6lyrics.com may offer additional features which require you to fill out forms requiring your personal information. We ask for your name, email address, city, country and birth date. The email address is used to send you a registration confirmation including activation link to active your account. The other personal details are used for display on your profile. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting patterns. Your IP address is also used to help diagnose technical problems. 6lyrics.com does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with any third parties. 

**For Parents Concerning the Privacy of Information on Their Children**   
We are a general audience site that does not knowingly collect data or accept registrations from children under 13 years of age. Currently, we do not collect any age-specific data on our site. If, in the future, we decide to collect any age-specific data on our site, we will, at a minimum, take reasonable steps to ensure that any users who may be under 13 years of age (and who attempt to complete the registration process on our site) are directed to another site within the 6lyrics.com family which specifically complies with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, or COPPA. 

**Cookies**   
Cookies are small text files that are used by many sites to store or transfer information between the main site and the computer you use to access the site. These cookies are stored in a special folder in your temporary internet files directory. 6lyrics.com uses cookies in parts of the website. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Advertisers**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. The advertisements may contain cookies. The advertisements are necessary to finance the costs of keeping this site online. 

**Links to Other Sites**   
We do not endorse and are not responsible for the content or practices of web sites operated by companies outside of 6lyrics.com that may be linked to this site. You should not assume that their privacy policies or practices are the same as those followed by our company or by other 6lyrics.com companies. Visitors to any such web sites should refer to their respective privacy policies and practices. 

**Changes in This Privacy Policy**   
We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we make changes that we consider material in our privacy practices, we will notify you in this space. We may also attempt to notify you of any such material changes to our privacy practices via email or by placing a notice on our home page. 

**Contact**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you are welcome to contact us. 

**Acceptance of This Privacy Policy**   
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Information by 6lyrics.com in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

_Effective as of March 1, 2009._

#### Poll of the Week

Poll submited by User: 

mashlieh

Which game are you more interested in?

Hockey  
Dodgeball  
Hide and seek  
Selector   
****************

Vote to see result

Click here to see more Polls
